<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<exercise>
  <rubric></rubric>
  <audio>data/1_content/listening/listening91.mp3</audio>
  <text>
    <![CDATA[<heading>48</heading>
      
      <p><b>Interviewer</b> How big is the Accor group?</p>
      <p><b>Manager</b> Well, we employ one hundred and seventy thousand people in nearly a hundred countries. And we have over four thousand hotels worldwide.</p>
      <p><b>Interviewer</b> So, very big.</p>
      <p><b>Manager</b> Yes, we are, but the hotel industry is very competitive – there are a lot of big chains out there.</p>
      <p><b>Interviewer</b> That's true. So, with so many competitors, how does Accor stay competitive? </p>
      <p><b>Manager</b> Well, one reason is that we are the only international group with hotels in every market segment. This means we can offer all our customers a wide choice. For example, Motel Six is a chain of budget hotels in North America. They offer the customer a cheap option. Then at the economy level there's the All Seasons brand in the Asia-Pacific region. You pay more at these hotels, but they offer very good service with friendly staff.</p>
      <p><b>Interviewer</b> What about hotels for the business traveller who wants more comfort and services?</p>
      <p><b>Manager</b> OK. This is the mid-range market segment. So, we're talking about hotels like Novotel. The quality at a Novotel hotel is very high with modern, up-to-date business facilities like meeting rooms and office services. Location is also important for the customer at these hotels so they are easy to find in city centres or at international airports. </p>
      <p><b>Interviewer</b> And what if money is no problem for the customer?</p>
      <p><b>Manager</b> Then you choose a Sofitel hotel. It's expensive, but it offers five-star quality and each one also offers the visitor something else. Because each country is different, every Sofitel hotel is different and gives the customer a special experience. </p>]]>
  </text>
</exercise>
